Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum C
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Consolidated General File, Series III
  - H - Hong Kong
    - Hong Kong Baptist College
      - Project evaluations, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 386)
      - Overseas personnel, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 387)
      - Proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 388-393)
      - Tse, Daniel C. W. (president, HKBC), 1980-1987 (Box 14, Folder 394)
      - Printed material, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 395)
    - Lingnan College
      - General, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 396)
  - I - India
    - General correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 14, Folder 397)
    - India Program: proposals, grants, correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 398-401)
    - India Program: grant proposals, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 401A)
    - India Program: grant proposals not approved, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 401B)
    - Indian Consultative Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 402)
    - AIACHE (All India Association for Christian Higher Education) - general correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 403-404)
    - AIACHE - proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 405-411)
    - AIACHE - printed material, 1980-1990 (Box 15, Folder 412)
    - AIACHE - printed material, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 1374)
    - AIACHE - Papers from Triennial Conference of Christian College Principals of India, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 412A)
    - Ahmednagar College, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 413)
    - Allahabad Agricultural Institute, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 414)
    - Assumption College, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 415)
    - Baring School - Baring Union Christian College, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 416)
    - Bishop Heber College (Box 15, Folder 417)
    - Christ Church College, 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 418)
    - Christian Medical College and Brown Memorial Hospital, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 419)
    - College of Social Work, Bombay, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 420)
    - Danielson Degree College, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 421)
    - Ewing Christian College, 1980-1986 (Box 15, Folder 422)
    - Holy Cross College, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 423)
    - Isabella Thoburn College, 1982-1990 (Box 15, Folder 424)
    - Jyoti Nivas College, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 425)
    - Loreto College, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 426)
    - Loyola College, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 427)
    - Lucknow Christian College, 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 428)
    - Madras Christian College - general corres., 1980-1986 (Box 15, Folder 429)
    - Madras Christian College - Dr. Augustine's visit, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 430)
    - Mar Thoma College, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 431)
    - Sophia College for Women, 1980-1990 (Box 15, Folder 432)
    - Sophia Wilson Community Counseling Center (Box 16, Folder 433)
    - St. Aloysius College, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 434)
    - St. John's College, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 435)
    - St. Joseph's College, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 436)
    - St. Xavier's College, Ahmedabad, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 437)
    - St. Xavier's College, Thumba, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 438)
    - Stella Maris College, 1983-1994 (Box 16, Folder 439)
    - Tamil Nadu Theological Seminary, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 440)
    - United Theological College, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 441)
    - Vellore Christian Medical College, 1980-1993 (Box 16, Folder 442-445)
    - Vellore Christian Medical College Board in NYC, 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 446-447)
    - Women's Christian College, Madras, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 448)
  - I - Indonesia
    - General
      - General file (Box 16, Folder 449)
      - Association of Catholic Institutes of Higher Education; previously known as ACAI: Association of Catholic Academic Institutions, 1981-1988 (Box 16, Folder 450-452)
      - Association of Indonesian Christian Higher Education, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 453)
      - Christian University of Indonesia, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 454)
      - Driyarkara Higher Institute of Philosophy, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 455)
      - Maranatha Christian University, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 456)
      - Methodist University of Indonesia, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 457)
    - Petra Christian University
      - AID/ ASHA, 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 458-459)
      - Five-year Development Plan, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 460)
      - Overseas Personnel, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 461)
      - Proposals, grants, 1980-1988 (Box 16, Folder 462-465)
      - Patty, O. F., 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 466-467)
      - Reports, Recommendation, Profiles, 1980-1987 (Box 16, Folder 468)
    - Satya Wacana Christian University
      - General correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 16, Folder 469)
      - AID/ ASHA grant, 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 470)
      - Background and evaluations, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 471)
      - Guidance and Counseling Center, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 472)
      - Kameo, Daniel (Development Officer), 1980 (Box 16, Folder 473)
      - Overseas Personnel, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 474)
      - Proposals, grants, reports, 1979-1987 (Box 17, Folder 475-480)
      - Sutarno, Dr., 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 481)
      - Toisuta, Willi, 1980-1986 (Box 17, Folder 482)
      - Wilardjo, Liek, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 483)
    - Nommensen University
      - General (Box 17, Folder 484)
      - Printed Matter, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 485)
      - Printed Matter (Box 17, Folder 486-487)
  - I - General
    - I (Box 17, Folder 488)
    - IBM Personal Computer Service Maintenance, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 489)
    - Ihromi, Tapi OMas, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 490)
    - Immanuel Congregational Church (UCC), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 491)
    - Imperial, Dr. and Mrs. George, 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 492)
    - Independent Sector (Box 17, Folder 493)
    - Institute A-Z (Box 17, Folder 494)
    - Institutional profiles (Box 17, Folder 495)
    - International A-Z (Box 17, Folder 496)
    - International Council of Community Churches, 1980-1987 (Box 17, Folder 497)
    - International Education Exchange, Council on, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 498)
    - International Foundation for Ewha Women's University, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 499)
    - Iowa, University of, 1980-1986 (Box 17, Folder 500)
    - Irvin, Dale T., 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 501)
    - Irving Trust Company, 1980-1988 (Box 17, Folder 502-503)
  - J - General
    - Jayasuriya, Nalini, 1985-1990 (Box 17, Folder 504)
    - John, K. C., 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 505)
    - John, V. V., 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 506)
    - Johnson, Ashby, 1980-1988 (Box 17, Folder 507)
    - Johnson, Craig B., 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 508)
    - Johnson Foundation's Wingspread Conference Center, 1980-1989 (Box 17, Folder 509)
    - Joyce, Dr. and Mrs. Richard E. (Raelyn), 1981-1987 (Box 17, Folder 510)
  - J - Japan
    - General correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 17, Folder 511)
    - International Christian University - corres. (Box 18, Folder 512)
    - International Christian University - proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 513-517)
    - Kwansei Gakuin Univ. Summer Student Program (Mark and Ruth Reames), 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 518)
    - Meiji Gakuin University, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 519)
    - Okinawa Christian Junior College, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 520)
    - Rikkyo (St. Paul's) University, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 521)
  - K - General
    - K, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 522)
    - Katoppo, Marianne, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 523)
    - Killough, Richard H. (Drury College), 1982-1987 (Box 18, Folder 524)
    - Kim, Prof. Hong-Myong and Dr. Jang Hajin, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 525)
    - Kim, Yong Joon, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 526)
    - Kim, Young Sulkun (estate of), 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 527)
    - King, Dr. and Mrs. James R. (Roy), 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 528)
    - Kleinjans, Everett, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 529)
    - Korea Legal AID Cneter for Family Relations, 1984-1988 (Box 18, Folder 530)
    - Korte, Charles D., 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 531)
    - Kramer, Martha M. (estate of), 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 532)
    - Kwok, Pui Lan, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 533)
    - Kwong, Wai Hong, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 534)
  - K - Korea
    - General
      - Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 535)
      - Dismissed professors: Korea Program (Box 18, Folder 536)
    - Ewha Woman's University
      - General correspondence, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 537)
      - International Foundation for Ewha University, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 538)
      - Kim, Okgill, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 539)
      - Korean Women's Institute, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 540)
      - Overseas personnel, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 541)
      - Proposals, grants, correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 542-544)
      - Publications and reports, 1980-1990 (Box 18, Folder 545)
    - Han nam University
      - Proposals, grants, 1982-1987 (Box 18, Folder 546-549)
    - Hanshin University
      - General, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 550)
    - Keimyung University
      - Proposals, grants, corres., 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 551-552)
      - Synn, Ilhi, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 553)
    - Presbyterian Medical Center
      - General, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 554)
    - Presbyterian Theological Seminary
      - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 555)
      - Third World Church Leadership Center, 1984-1987 (Box 18, Folder 556)
    - Sacred Heart College for Women
      - General, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 557)
    - Seoul National University, College of Music
      - General, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 558)
    - Seoul Woman's College
      - Koh, Whang-Kyung (President), 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 559)
      - Overseas personnel, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 560)
      - Proposals, grants, correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 561-562)
      - Publications and reports, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 563)
    - Sogang University
      - General correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 564)
      - Mace, Fr. John D., 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 565)
      - Overseas personnel, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 566)
      - Proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 567-573)
      - Publications and printed matter, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 574)
      - Questionnaire and evaluation, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 575)
      - Skillingstad, M. Delmar, 1980-1989 (Box 19, Folder 576-577)
    - Songsim College for Women
      - Koh, Do-Yim, President, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 578)
    - Soong Jun University
      - General correspondence, 1980-1988 (Box 19, Folder 579)
      - AID/ ASHA application, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 580)
      - Background, profile, quetionnaire, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 581)
      - Kang, Shin-Myung, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 582)
      - Koh, Bum Soe, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 583)
      - Overseas personnel, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 584)
      - Prince, Jack, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 585)
      - Proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 586-591)
    - Yonsei University
      - General correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 19, Folder 592)
      - Cho, Yohan (Yohan Cho Scholarship), 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 593)
      - Dentistry, College of, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 594)
      - Lee, Hyoung Heang, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 595)
      - Lee, Woo Choo, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 596)
      - Medicine, College of: General correspondence, 1980-1895 (Box 19, Folder 597)
      - Medicine, College of: Class of 1956 Alumni Association, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 598)
      - Medicine, College of: Class of 1960 Fund, 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 599)
      - Medicine, College of: Endowment Fund, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 600)
      - Medicine, College of: Nursing, College of, 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 601)
      - Medicine, College of: Rehabilitation Medicne, 1980-1984 (Box 19, Folder 602)
      - Medicine, College of: Severance Hospital (Box 19, Folder 603)
      - Overseas personnel, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 604)
      - Paik, George (Box 19, Folder 605)
      - Proposals, grants, reports, 1981-1986 (Box 19, Folder 606-610)
      - Proposals, grants, reports, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 611)
      - Publications and printed matter, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 612)
      - Reports, profiles, questionnaires, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 613)
      - Underwood, Horace G., 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 614-615)
      - Urban Studies Development Institute (Dr. Chung-Hyun Ro), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 616)
  - L - General
    - L - Le (Box 20, Folder 617)
    - Li - Lu (Box 20, Folder 618)
    - Laird, Mary Adams (estate of), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 619)
    - Landesmon, Louis (National University of Singapore), 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 620)
    - Lane, Ortha M., 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 621)
    - Larsen, Herman A., 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 622)
    - Lau, Dr. and Mrs. Kenneth K., 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 623)
    - Law, Susan G., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 624)
    - Layague, Caroline (Memorial Scholarship), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 625)
    - Lee, Hahn Been, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 626)
    - Lerrigo, Edith M., 1980-1989 (Box 20, Folder 627)
    - Li, Yan, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 628)
    - Liang, Hubert S., 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 629)
    - Lim, Thomas P. K., 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 630)
    - Lim, Dr. and Mrs. Ungki (Asia-N. America visiting scholars), 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 631)
    - Lin, Dr. Edgar (U.S.- Taiwan Environmental Institute), 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 632)
    - Lingnan University, 1980-1988 (Box 20, Folder 633)
    - Lisk, Georgina C., 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 634)
    - Liu, Dr. and Mrs. Chien, 1980-1988 (Box 20, Folder 635)
    - Lo, Ruth Earnshaw, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 636)
    - Lockett, Mrs. W. B., 1980-1987 (Box 20, Folder 637)
    - Long, Charles H. (Forward Movement Publications), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 638)
    - Lopulisa, Mr. and Mrs. Shirley Cloves, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 639)
    - Love, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, Chosen Mission Project, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 641)
    - Luce, Henry, III, 1978-1987 (Box 20, Folder 642)
    - Luidens, Edwin M., 1980-1987 (Box 20, Folder 643)
    - Lutheran A-Z (Box 20, Folder 644)
    - Luzares, Casilda, 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 645)
  - M - General
    - Ma, Mrs. Dawang, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 646)
    - Magdamo, Priscilla, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 647)
    - Maguire, John D., 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 648)
    - Marquis, Sarah Travel Service, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 649)
    - Marshall, Mr. and Mrs. Irl, 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 650)
    - McComb, Donald, 1980-1991 (Box 20, Folder 651)
    - McCord, Dr. and Mrs. James I., 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 652)
    - McCormick Theological Seminary, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 653)
    - McDermott, Joseph Peter, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 654)
    - McKeever, Mr. and Mrs. Porter (Susan) (Box 20, Folder 655)
    - Meacham, Dr. and Mrs. Robert, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 656)
    - Meldrim, John W., 1983 (Box 20, Folder 657)
    - Mendoza, Everett, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 658)
    - Mesevage, Thomas, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 659)
    - Meuwissen, E. J. M., 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 660)
    - Millett, Fred J., 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 661)
    - Mills, Emily Case (estate of), 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 662)
    - Mitchell, Ruth Crawford, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 663)
    - Moffett, Samuel, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 664)
    - Montgomery, Lola J., 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 665)
    - Mook, Dr. and Mrs. Telfer (Jane), 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 666)
    - Moore, Mrs. Maurice T. - General correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 667)
    - Moore, Mrs. Maurice T. - Elisabeth Luce Moore Asian Professorship (Box 21, Folder 668)
    - Morgan, Gertrude W. (estate of), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 669)
    - Morris, Harriet, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 670)
    - Morro Bay United Presbyterian Church, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 671)
    - Mott, George Fox (Greater Washington Council), 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 672)
    - Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company, 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 673)
    - Mutual of Omaha, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 674)
  - N - General
    - N (Box 21, Folder 675)
    - Najera, Edmund, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 676)
    - National Council of Churches - finance, proposals, grants, 1980-1988 (Box 21, Folder 677)
    - NCC - Luidens, Edwin M. (Office for E. Asia and the Pacific), 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 678)
    - NCC - Task Force on Militarization in Indochina Misc. areas, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 679-680)
    - Netherlands A-Z (Box 21, Folder 681)
    - New Horizons Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 682)
    - New York Dental Service Corporation, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 683)
    - New York State Department of Law (Box 21, Folder 684)
    - New York Life Insurance Company, 1980-1987 (Box 21, Folder 685)
    - Ng, Dr. and Mrs. Lee Ming (Jeannie Lee), 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 686)
    - Niebaum, Julia M. (estate of), 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 687)
    - Noren, Dr. Loren E. (Ruth), 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 688)
    - Northrup, Robert W. (Japan-N. Am. Comm. on Cooperative Mission), 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 689)
    - Nottingham, William J. (Christian Church - Disciples of Christ), 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 690)
  - O - General
    - O (Box 21, Folder 691)
    - Oberlin College A-Z (Box 21, Folder 692)
    - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association, 1980-1987 (Box 21, Folder 693)
    - OBOR (Mr. Ivan Kats, Director), 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 694)
    - Overholt, William A., 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 695)
  - P - General
    - P (Box 21, Folder 696)
    - Padelford, Dr. and Mrs. Norman J., 1980-1988 (Box 21, Folder 697)
    - Pakistan, Christian Study Centre, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 698)
    - Palmer, Robert B., 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 699)
    - Pantejo, Edmundo A., 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 700)
    - Park, Tae Sun, 1980-1986 (Box 21, Folder 701)
    - Parker, George F., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 702)
    - Parsonage, Robert R., 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 703)
    - Petersen, Dr. and Mrs. Arnold J., 1979-1983 (Box 21, Folder 704-705)
    - Pew, J. Howard Freedom Trust, 1981-1988 (Box 21, Folder 706)
    - Pittau, Joseph, S.J., 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 707)
    - Poocharoen, Boonthong, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 708)
    - Presbyterian Church in Taiwan (Chun Ming Kao, General Secretary), 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 709)
    - Price Waterhouse Co., 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 710)
    - Princeton-in-Asia, 1980-1988 (Box 21, Folder 711)
  - P - Philippines
    - General
      - General correspondence (Box 22, Folder 712)
      - Asian Institute for Liturgy and Music (Box 22, Folder 713)
      - ACSC (Assoc. of Christian Schools and College) - proposals, grants, 1980-1988 (Box 22, Folder 714-715)
      - ACSC - proposals, reports, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 1376)
      - ACSC - correspondence, 1980-1991 (Box 22, Folder 716-717)
      - Ateneo de Manila University, 1980-1989 (Box 22, Folder 718)
      - Christ the King College, 1982-1985 (Box 22, Folder 719)
      - Coordination Center for Research and Development, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 720)
      - Dansalan Agricultural Center and Community Service (Box 22, Folder 721)
      - Dansalan College Foundation, 1981-1993 (Box 22, Folder 722-724)
      - Dansalan/ Gowing Memorial Research Center, 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 725)
      - Dansalan Junior College, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 726)
      - Dansalan Research Center, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 727)
      - De La Salle University: China Studies Program, 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 728)
      - De La Salle University: General correspondence (Box 22, Folder 729-730)
      - De La Salle University: Proposals, grants, 1980-1989 (Box 22, Folder 731-736)
      - De La Salle University: Publications and reports, 1980-1990 (Box 22, Folder 737)
      - FIMFS (Federation of Instituitons for Marine Freshwater Science), 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 738)
      - Government of the Philippines, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 739)
      - Grace Christian High School (Mrs. Julia Tan), 1983 (Box 22, Folder 740)
      - Immaculate Conception College (Sr. Ma. Irmina Roa), 1980-1985 (Box 22, Folder 741)
      - Inter-Institutional Consortium, 1980-1986 (Box 22, Folder 742-747)
      - Maryknoll College, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 748)
      - Mindanao Forum, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 749)
      - Miriam College Foundation, Inc. (Quezon City), 1989-1993 (Box 23, Folder 750)
      - St. Scholastica's College, Manila, 1982-1987 (Box 23, Folder 751)
      - Southeast Asia Institute for Liturgy and Music, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 752)
      - UGAT (National organization of anthropologists in the Philippines) (Box 23, Folder 753)
      - United Church of Christ in the Philippines, 1981-1987 (Box 23, Folder 754)
      - United Missionary Office, 1980-1990 (Box 23, Folder 755-756)
      - University of the Philippines, Diliman, 1980-1986 (Box 23, Folder 757)
      - University of the Philippines, Los Banos, 1980-1986 (Box 23, Folder 758)
      - University of San Carlos, Cebu City (Box 23, Folder 759)
      - Visayas State College of Agriculture, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 760)
    - Central Philippine Unversity
      - Reports, corres., proposals, grants, 1979-1989 (Box 23, Folder 761-769)
      - Report on projects, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1377)
      - Engineering reports - Dr. Glade Wilcox, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 770)
      - Women's Resource Center (Box 23, Folder 771)
      - Printed matter, 1980-1990 (Box 23, Folder 772)
    - Northern Christian College
      - Correspondence, proposals, grants, 1978-1987 (Box 23, Folder 773-779)
      - Presidents' reports: Lagon, Filemon, 1980-1987 (Box 23, Folder 780)
      - Publications (Box 23, Folder 781)
      - Five-year development plan (Box 23, Folder 782)
      - Multi-purpose/ library building (Box 23, Folder 783)
    - Philippine Christian University
      - Correspondence, proposals, grants, 1980-1987 (Box 24, Folder 784-789)
      - Seminar report, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 1378)
      - Arquiza, Lino Q, 1980-1986 (Box 24, Folder 790-791)
      - Carino, F. V., 1982-1986 (Box 24, Folder 792)
      - Publications (Box 24, Folder 793)
      - Tayko, Oscar J., 1980-1986 (Box 24, Folder 794)
      - Union Theological Seminary, 1980-1987 (Box 24, Folder 795)
    - Silliman University
      - Alcala, Angel C., 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 796-797)
      - Aldecoa, Judge Venancia, 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 798)
      - Apilado, Mariano C., 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 799)
      - Auditors' reports, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 800)
      - Ausego, Luz U., 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 801)
      - Cornelio, Josefina, 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 802)
      - Correspondence, general (Box 24, Folder 803)
      - Creative Writers Workshop, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 804)
      - Divinity School, 1980-1988 (Box 24, Folder 805)
      - Doromal, Quintin S., 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 806)
      - Dulamal, Rajan B. (Medical Center), 1984-1989 (Box 24, Folder 807)
      - Elwood, Dr. and Mrs. Douglas (Bettie), 1980-1993 (Box 24, Folder 808)
      - Endowment Fund, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 809)
      - Faurot, Albert, 1980-1989 (Box 24, Folder 810)
      - Financial correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box 24, Folder 811-815)
      - Honors Program (Box 24, Folder 816)
      - Law, Dale, 1980-1988 (Box 24, Folder 817)
      - Magbanua, Juanito T., 1981-1991 (Box 24, Folder 818)
      - Malayang, Ben S. III, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 819)
      - Martinez, Salvador T. (Buddy), 1980-1987 (Box 24, Folder 820)
      - Maslog, Crispin (School of Communication), 1980-1987 (Box 24, Folder 821)
      - Medical Center (Box 24, Folder 822-823)
      - Music and Fine Arts, School of (Box 24, Folder 824)
      - Nursing, College of, 1980-1987 (Box 24, Folder 825)
      - Palmore, James A., 1980-1986 (Box 24, Folder 826)
      - Publications, 1980-1991 (Box 24, Folder 827)
      - "Present situation at Silliman", 1985 (Box 25, Folder 828)
      - "Crisis at S.U. following the election of Aldecoa", 1983 Nov (Box 25, Folder 829)
      - Proposals and grants, 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 830-835)
      - Reynolds, Hubert, 1980-1992 (Box 25, Folder 836)